亲爱的
Sweet pea
我揉着我的眼睛
I blow my eyes
不知何时也不知为何
Don't know when and I don't know why
你是我回家的唯一原因
You're the only reason I keep on coming home
亲爱的
Sweet pea
关于这些事
What's all this about
你不要都小题大做
Don't get what you want all you do is fuss and pout
你是我回家的唯一原因
You're the only reason I keep on coming home
我喜欢你买给她的唱片
I like the record you bought her
我总是犹豫不决
I always seem to falter
这些话总是含在嘴里
And the words just get in the way
我知道我将要崩溃
Oh I know I'm gonna crumble
我试着保持谦卑
I'm trying to stay humble
但从来不深思熟虑
But I never think before I see
亲爱的
Sweet pea
你拥有我的灵魂
Keeper of my soul
我知道我有时会失控
I know sometimes I'm out of control
你是我回家的
You're the only reason I keep on coming
你是我回家的唯一原因
You're the only reason I keep on coming home